<?xml version="1.0"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
  <title>MY THOUGHTS ARE YOURS</title>
  <link href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc"/>
  <link type="application/atom+xml" rel="self" href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/atom.xml"/>
  <updated>2012-06-24T15:45:57-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc</id>
  <author>
    <name>YOLK</name>
    <email>mythoughtsareyours@yolk.cc</email>
  </author>

  
  <entry>
    <id>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2012/06/24/LAST-CHANCE</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2012/06/24/LAST-CHANCE.html"/>
    <title>LAST CHANCE</title>
    <published>2012-06-24T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2012-06-24T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>YOLK</name>
      <uri>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dream game in which the player is able to create a physical universe by exploiting current level universe. Example: Player sits on ledge and falls backwards, not dying or causing physical impact but slipping through the perfect quantitized and fractalized crack that exists in our universe. If you could only be aware of it.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2012/06/09/A-MATTER-OF-SPACE-AND-TIME</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2012/06/09/A-MATTER-OF-SPACE-AND-TIME.html"/>
    <title>A matter of space and time</title>
    <published>2012-06-09T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2012-06-09T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>YOLK</name>
      <uri>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Reality is a hard thing to comprehend. Take into account new findings in the bleeding-edge of physics; you may become even more confused. All things obey the laws of physics except when they become very small. At that scale it seems as though our simple act of viewing an electron determines it’s place in space and time. Almost as if our consciousness’ stream disrupted that electron’s wave while it appears briefly in our universe or our reality. The multi-verse theory states that there are an infinite amount of universes all contained within one ultra-verse. This is a hard thing for a single person to comprehend. In the facet of human experience and how we actually exist on this earth, how will we ever hope to understand something more complicated than ourselves, the realm of psychology and neurology seems to be self-contradicting; as if anyone in the human race would be able to deconstruct a brain and learn how it works. An inherent paradox – how can a being determine how itself can function? Would it not require a larger, more complex brain to understand the way the brains in us humans work now? And what if that “larger-brained” being needs to have brain surgery, would they also need an even larger-brained being to understand their brain? How would any of the world’s problems be solved? (If Atlas holds the world on his shoulders, whom holds Atlas?) The problem is recursive and replicating. The problems seem too big for a simple mind, or a single individual to tackle. Yet it is happening, the world is wonderful today. There has been more progress in the last 100 years than there has been for the entire history of the human race. Progress is becoming exponentially faster and more advanced. These problems are being solved through collaboration, many heads tackling the same problem. Through collaboration, large problems are tackled and eventually solved, or resolved in some matter.Research groups are the prime example for an artist uneasy about any sort of collaboration. It’s as if they still believe that being an artist still means going recluse for 5 years and coming out with some body of work. It is not only unnecessary, but also irresponsible to be stagnant. There is no reason any longer to say, “I don’t know how to do this.” Our minds are built to be scared of a simple problem of asking for help because we no longer make a distinction to any other problem in the world. Asking for help is not a bear that wants to eat you, even though the lizard part of your brain may believe that to be the case, which in turn creates problems such as procrastination or Sophophobia which is the fear of learning. By sharing my current work, future projects and the process in which I create an abstract feeling that a work should “feel” like. The end result is subject to change with time. That is the nature of research, continuously changing the nature of the “process” to accomplish an end result – or for an artist, work. As I believe technology is a technique in art, I would like to know where my work stands as a tool as communication of expression. Is it aesthetically pleasing or does the work seem cold, calculated, and mathematical.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2012/06/05/CRYOGENIC_SLEEP</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2012/06/05/CRYOGENIC_SLEEP.html"/>
    <title>I WOKE UP FROM A CRYOGENIC SLEEP</title>
    <published>2012-06-05T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2012-06-05T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>YOLK</name>
      <uri>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I woke up from a cryogenic sleep. The world was in disarray. The entire population of living creatures were wiped out by an alien race. The alien race coated the world in this deadly energy. They almost killed everything on planet earth. People knew what was going to happen so they threw 1 male and 1 female into this shelter. They were responsible for seeding the entire population of the human race once more. I didn’t find out what they looked like until there were several children. The new human race was supposed to be seeded by an ugly man and woman. Luckily however they were still groups of people that survived. These included a group of old ladies that were trying to fix the internet. And a group of people I knew and liked. I was afraid that the internet was going to be dominated by the guy from “Big Guy and Rusty” (The guy that turned into a very big brain and ate people’s thoughts.) But instead of being completely organic he was mostly machine. (With a very cool color scheme and material of black and white.)&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2012/05/12/ImpercepitbleDisasters</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2012/05/12/ImpercepitbleDisasters.html"/>
    <title>Imperceptible disasters of the cosmic dilemma.</title>
    <published>2012-05-12T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2012-05-12T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>YOLK</name>
      <uri>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Imperceptible dilemma wherein there are several perceivable paths of closure. Moreover, however, the most perceived - and perceptually viable - is the natural instinction or was I alone.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2012/05/04/UNSETTLEDDOMINANCE</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2012/05/04/UNSETTLEDDOMINANCE.html"/>
    <title>UNSETTLED DOMINANCE</title>
    <published>2012-05-04T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2012-05-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>YOLK</name>
      <uri>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Unknown scholars and entrepreneurs agree that in order for the manifestation of a new reality there is a small requirement for a re-initialization upon the current stack of horrors. When the sky falls and the world crumbles are we expected to be another role player in someone else&amp;#8217;s dream? Are we inherently nothing more than a subconscious, and outer-universe zeitgeist of consciousness that is beyond our understanding. We may just be numb and stupid all the while we are conscious tendrils of a higher being that does not exist. Considering the theory of multiple universes as well as string theory one may get the idea that the universe is hard deterministic but I am not sure that this is right. We may be the only universe that has been able to achieve sentience but aren&amp;#8217;t we no more than a small temporal life span on this small planet in this small galaxy within our universe which is a part of our &amp;#8220;Ultraverse&amp;#8221;, the theoretical plane where multiple universes coincide. Will we never be able to look out of our universe? Will we ever be able to look into a black hole?&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2012/05/04/TrappedInAClutchOfObfuscatedOptimism</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2012/05/04/TrappedInAClutchOfObfuscatedOptimism.html"/>
    <title>Trapped in a clutch of obfuscated optimism</title>
    <published>2012-05-04T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2012-05-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>YOLK</name>
      <uri>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Trapped in a clutch of obfuscated optimistic intent; I was stuck here to witness the endless, silent scream of a horrid that was once not known to this world. A scream and a shout were all that were between me living and my enlightened for what they don&amp;#8217;t describe to you when you are touched by the ether of power – you become it as well.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/10/17/UnsentMessage20111011</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/10/17/UnsentMessage20111011.html"/>
    <title>Unsent Message - 20111011</title>
    <published>2011-10-17T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2011-10-17T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>YOLK</name>
      <uri>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I am not trying to deconstruct you, I am just trying to relate. Please don&amp;#8217;t mistake my last message ad negative. I actually think all the time. So I totally understand where you are coming from.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/09/12/ThinkOfLife</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/09/12/ThinkOfLife.html"/>
    <title>Think of Life</title>
    <published>2011-09-12T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2011-09-12T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>YOLK</name>
      <uri>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Think of life. One spark can consume endless amounts of fuel if the conditions are right. Reactions are never-ending, spreading out from its origin. Now think of this as perception. One spark that interacts with reality can endlessly consume what surrounds it. Now this can become a problem, control-wise, but I do keep it under control with little effort. What does need to be done, is several “perceptual sparks” at once. No matter how much I add, it never takes any effort&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/09/12/SoDamnGentle</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/09/12/SoDamnGentle.html"/>
    <title>So damn gentle with everything.</title>
    <published>2011-09-12T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2011-09-12T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>YOLK</name>
      <uri>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have to be so damn gentle with everything. How much tension builds up when one has to go through the world knowing if they’re not too careful. “You will have everything shatter into a million pieces!” Life is so fragile. If it wasn’t perfectly balance we would not be here. Then again you might say that there is a room for error, but compared to the cosmos this margin for error is miniscule. I am here, now. I need to break through the limiter that stresses my brain. It’s not their fault for what I am. I am what I am.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/09/05/InOrderforRealitytoChange</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/09/05/InOrderforRealitytoChange.html"/>
    <title>In Order For Reality to Change</title>
    <published>2011-09-05T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2011-09-05T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>YOLK</name>
      <uri>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In order for reality to change, all beings experiencing such reality must agree upon a concocted truth. In the scope of our own intelligence, a being could not conceive of something that does not already exist in our reality.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/09/04/WhatIfForSomeReason</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/09/04/WhatIfForSomeReason.html"/>
    <title>What if, for some reason?</title>
    <published>2011-09-04T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2011-09-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>YOLK</name>
      <uri>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;What if. For some reason I were to realize that throughout the day, the majority of the customers that I serve are a figment of my imagination. The real ones I serve are the hallucinations, the real ones are instantly forgotten. There would exist a balance between the two, for every hallucination I had, there had to be an equal (in time) memory that had to be lost. The hallucination would fit right where the original memory used to be. Then my hallucinations are memories. So who says they’re not real. I wouldn’t know the difference. If I were to ever have a conversation with you. You explaining to me, “Those memories aren’t real Joe, that never happened!” I would say to you, “Reality is happening all the time. As soon as something exists, it no longer exists - that is the essence of flow and time. Saying something “never happened” is saying that there exists choice. If I chose for something not to exist in my memory - then it never happened. What I need to do is stop remembering the memories which make it untrue.” Am I crazy?&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/09/04/SolarPlexus</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/09/04/SolarPlexus.html"/>
    <title>Solar Plexus</title>
    <published>2011-09-04T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2011-09-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>YOLK</name>
      <uri>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The third eye, solar plexus, what a wonderful thing. It is the only thing that recently gave me a totally different experience. It started at the plexus, and travelled through my brain right down to the tail of my spine. When un-merged from the water I felt a euphoria and my muscles relaxed. Am I stressed? Who knows.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/09/04/RealityAndMyGrip</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/09/04/RealityAndMyGrip.html"/>
    <title>Reality, and my grip becoming lose.</title>
    <published>2011-09-04T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2011-09-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>YOLK</name>
      <uri>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Reality is becoming more and more like a dream each day. What I feel in life is just as bland and unfeeling as in a dream… I fear I am losing lucidity. Reality is getting harder to distinguish from my dreams. I lay here and think. I think and wonder, “Am I a self-conscious being or an animal that survives on instincts?” An animal of highly-compacted intelligence which survives on instinct could be perceived as a conscious being. I lay here unaware of time passing by. It all seems the same. Where is my life, no where is reality going?&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/09/04/InSilenceForever</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/09/04/InSilenceForever.html"/>
    <title>In Silence, Forever</title>
    <published>2011-09-04T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2011-09-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>YOLK</name>
      <uri>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In Silence Forever If I scream, nobody will listen. If I cry, no one will care. I am to spend the rest of my days in silence, I am unable to act upon any of my desires. I am forced to do nothing and hope the decisions of others will achieve my intended goals in the end.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <id>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/09/04/AsWouldAllTheyBeDamned</id>
    <link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc/2011/09/04/AsWouldAllTheyBeDamned.html"/>
    <title>As would all they be damned</title>
    <published>2011-09-04T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2011-09-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>YOLK</name>
      <uri>http://mythoughtsareyours.yolk.cc</uri>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As would all they be damned. The world in strife. I am, therefore you are not. I am nothing. You were never anything. Forever, I am done.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  
 
</feed>
